dairyqueen.com 2017-05-03

# Privacy Statement - Dairy Queen

Effective March 15, 2016

This privacy statement applies to the following websites: dairyqueen.com, dq.com, dq.ca, orangejulius.com, dqcakes.com.

Please read this privacy statement carefully, because by using any of these websites, you accept and agree to the terms stated below. We may change the terms of this privacy statement at any time, and the continued use of this site is your agreement to any change in the privacy statement.

## Collection & Use of Information

We collect information through our website in several different ways.

**Information You Submit.** You give us personal information when you join one of our loyalty clubs, enter one of our surveys, contests or sweepstakes, if you submit a question, comment or complaint,if you request or submit information about becoming a franchisee, if you submit an employment application, or for an online cake order. “Personal information” means any information about an identifiable individual, such as name, address, phone number, email, birth date, or gender. Except with your consent or as required or permitted by law, we will use the information you submit for the purposes for which it is submitted or as otherwise described in this privacy statement. If you join one of our loyalty clubs, you may receive newsletters, email or special offers, which you may unsubscribe from at any time using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.

Most of our locations are independently owned and operated franchises, and we do not own or operate these locations. Comments, questions or complaints submitted to us about a specific location will be forwarded to the franchised location, along with any contact information you provide with your comment. If you have comments regarding a specific location, we recommend you contact that location directly so that they may personally and immediately assist you. We do not guarantee the privacy practices of any specific franchised location.

**Information Collected By Automated Means.** We collect and use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. In some circumstances, an IP address may be considered personal information. We also collect information through the use of cookies. Cookies are pieces of data your web browser stores on your hard drive that we use to improve your user experience on our website. We and our third party vendors may also use cookies to provide you with our advertising messages on other websites you visit; these third party vendors may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites based on these cookies. These activities provide us with important marketing information and lets us know how we are doing at attracting new visitors and maintaining relationships with our existing visitors. If you wish, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or delete any existing cookies from your computer, but this may negatively impact your experience on our website. Our third party vendors may collect additional information by automated means when you visit our website, such as browser type or operating system.

**Information About Third-Party Cookies and Interest-Based Advertising**  
In addition to the cookies we deliver to your computer or mobile device through this website, certain third parties may deliver cookies to you for a variety of reasons. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand how visitors engage with our websites. To learn more about Google Analytics, [click here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html). Other third parties may deliver cookies to your computer or mobile device for the purpose of tracking your online behaviors over time and across nonaffiliated websites and/or delivering targeted advertisements either on this website or on other websites.

You have choices about the collection of information by third parties on our websites. For example, if you don't want information about your visit to this website sent to Google Analytics, you may download an Opt-out Browser Add-on by [clicking here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). Please note that this Add-on does not prevent information from being sent to us.

In addition, if you would like to opt out of having participating entities collect your online behavior for advertising purposes when you are browsing our websites, [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) for a "Website Opt Out." You will be directed to an industry-developed website that allows you to choose whether each listed entity may collect and use data for interest-based advertising purposes. It may be that some of the third parties that collect interest-based information on this website do not participate in the Website Opt Out, in which case the best way to avoid third-party tracking of your online behaviors may be through your browser settings and deletion of cookies.

The Website Opt Out described above works only on websites. To opt out of having participating entities track your behaviors for advertising purposes when you are using our mobile apps, download and use the Digital Advertising Alliance's "App Choices" app. As with the Website Opt Out, the "Mobile App Opt Out" prevents tracking only by participating entities.

Please note that the Website Opt Out and Mobile App Opt Out are device specific. If you wish to opt-out from having interest-based information collected by participating entities across all devices, you need take the steps outlined above from each device.

**Sharing Information**  
We may share personal information within the _DQ_ _®_ / _Orange Julius_ ® family of companies, which includes American Dairy Queen Corporation and Orange Julius of America, which are U.S. based companies, and Dairy Queen Canada Inc. and Orange Julius Canada Limited, which are Canadian companies, and any of their affiliates. Information collected from this website will be received in the United States. Information shared within the _DQ_ / _Orange Julius_ family will comply with this privacy statement.

Cakes ordered through our dqcakes.com website are prepared at a _DQ_ location, which are independently owned and operated franchises. We will share your cake order information, which may include the contact information you provide, to a franchised location for purposes of tracking, responding to, and fulfilling your order.

We may share your personal information with third parties:

  1. To provide services to you, such as purchasing and shipping goods, or credit card processing;

  2. In connection with services provided to us, such as hosting, data management and storage, marketing or remarketing, website or marketing analytics, email services for our loyalty clubs, services to assist us with responding to you if you send us a comment, question, or complaint, for contest or sweepstakes administration and fulfillment, for employment application processing, and other similar services. We and our third party service providers may use servers in the U.S. or another country. Your personal information may be processed and stored in the U.S. or another country, and the government, courts, law enforcement or regulatory agencies of that country may by law be able to obtain your personal information;

  3. For purposes of improving your user experience across our different websites and platforms (such as our mobile app);

  4. We use Zipscene LLC to help us operate our mobile app and administer various activities. To learn more about how Zipscene LLC uses information you provide to us, please visit [zipscene.com/privacy](http://www.zipscene.com/privacy);

  5. For purposes of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization (including professional advisors involved in completing such a transaction). You agree that any of our successors may use and disclose the information for the same purposes as described in this statement; or

  6. As required by law, or as needed to cooperate in or defend against any law enforcement investigation or legal proceeding.

We may share aggregated demographic information (data that cannot identify an individual person) with our third party vendors and advertisers.

If you participate in a contest or sweepstakes, we may publish information about you such as your name, city of residence or prize winnings.

**California Disclosures**  
California’s Business and Professions Code section 22575 requires us to disclose how we respond to “do not track” signals. We currently take no action to respond to “do not track” signals.

Under section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business with whom the California resident has established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year.  
To request this information, contact privacy@idq.com.

**Links**  
This website may contain links to third party websites that we do not own, including links on our website to purchase _DQ_ or _Orange Julius_ gift cards or merchandise. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites, and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personal information from you. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Franchisee Websites**  
Many _DQ_ and _Orange Julius_ locations are independently owned and operated businesses and may have their own websites. This privacy statement does not apply to sites run by independently owned and operated locations.

**Children’s Privacy**  
We may have separate websites directed toward children. Our privacy practices regarding children will be posted on those websites.

**Mobile App**  
If you download the official _DQ®_ mobile app, our privacy policy regarding use of the app is available within the app. There may be other _DQ_ or _Orange Julius_ branded apps run by our franchisees, and our privacy policies do not apply to those apps.

**Security**  
We take security measures to protect personal information that we maintain against theft, unauthorized access, or alteration.

**Feedback**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement, our privacy practices, or your personal information that is under our control, please contact us at:

Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer  
International Dairy Queen, Inc.  
7505 Metro Blvd  
Minneapolis, MN 55439  
Email: privacy@idq.com

**Visitor Agreement**  
Your use of this site is also subject to our [Visitor Agreement](http://www.dairyqueen.com/us-en/Visitor-Agreement/).
